ideafit.com 2019-05-09

# 

IDEA understands how important privacy is to our users. We are committed to protecting your privacy and want to make sure that you understand how your information is used. We also want you to be aware that you have choices about how we use this information. 

What Information We Collect: When you create a user account, we ask for basic information such as your name, address, e-mail address, and other contact information. We keep track of your participation in IDEA events and member services (like liability insurance, etc.) so we can understand our users’ interests and evaluate the effectiveness of our offerings. Similarly, we keep track of your usage of IDEA's website and services, as well as your comments and feedback, in order to continually improve the quality of IDEA's website and services. To that end, we also reserve the right to collect and associate with our users any information that they disclose while using our website. We also collect demographic information from other sources to help us learn more about member characteristics and needs. In addition, we may ask for additional information in your visits to www.ideafit.com. All of this information helps us better serve our users and improve our programs. In the event you want to change any of your personal information with IDEA, simply contact us at the address listed below. 

As a way of providing additional user value, we ask for your e-mail address so that you may receive the IDEA Newsletters and other e-mail communications on a regular basis. This helps the Association control our mailing expenses and communicate with users. We do not support e-mail SPAM in any form and provide an easy subscriber "opt-out" on every e-mail we send. 

Information Sharing: We share your mailing list information (name & address) only with companies that we believe are reputable and have beneficial products or services that are of value to IDEA members. Some of the providers of IDEA member services, including some of those listed on our Member Services and Discounts area, pay a fee for access to our mailing list. Our contracts with these companies require them to keep the mailing list information strictly confidential. We do not sell or rent the mailing list to telemarketers or mailing list brokers. Finally, we may release personal member information on the rare occasions when we are required to do so by law, or when necessary or appropriate to comply with legal process or to protect or defend IDEA and its members. 

We may offer joint promotions or programs that, in order for your participation, will require us to share your information with third parties. We may collect a share of sales or other compensation from third-party links (via e-commerce affiliate linking) on our websites or digital entities. In fulfilling these types of promotions, we may share your name and other information in connection with fulfilling the incentive. These third party sites/companies have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these sites/companies. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of IDEA and welcome any feedback about these sites/companies. 

We respect your choices. If you do not want us to share your name and address information with providers of IDEA member services, you can contact us as specified below. 

Contact Us:  
IDEA Health & Fitness Association  
10190 Telesis Court  
San Diego, CA 92121

E-mail: contact@ideafit.com 

This privacy policy is effective as of June 15, 2010. IDEA reserves the right to change its privacy policy at any time. In the event the privacy policy is changed, the most recent version of the privacy policy will be posted on ideafit.com.
